Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1960-2001; Accession 2014-M-053
  - Mayoral records
    - 1965 Campaign records
      - Campaign literature
        - Press releases, 1965 July (Box 3, Folder 11)
        - Press releases, 1965 August (Box 3, Folder 12)
        - Press releases, 1965 September (Box 3, Folder 13)
        - Press releases, 1965 October 1-19 (Box 3, Folder 14)
        - Press releases, 1965 October 20-31 (Box 3, Folder 15)
      - Contact lists
        - Campaign workers, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 1)
        - Assembly district contacts, Circa 1965 (Box 4, Folder 2)
        - Assembly district workers, 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 3)
        - Assembly districts and election districts, Circa 1965 (Box 4, Folder 4)
        - Districts 19-30, Circa 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
        - Districts 31-50, Circa 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
        - Districts 51-70, Circa 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 7)
        - Districts 71-86, Circa 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Position papers and campaign platform
        - Crime, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 9)
        - Economy, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 10)
        - Education, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 11)
        - Health, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 12)
        - Housing, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
        - Issues book, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
        - Mollen-Costello, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 4)
        - Organization of New York City government, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
        - Parks and recreation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
        - Position papers - General, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 7)
        - Poverty, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 8)
        - Puerto Rican Community, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
        - Small business, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
        - Transportation, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
      - Campaign operations and volunteer training materials
        - Campaign headquarters manuals, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 12)
        - Campaign operations, districts 20-24, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
        - Campaign operations, districts 26-34, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
        - Campaign operations, districts 35-39, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
        - Campaign operations, districts 40-49, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 16)
        - Campaign operations, districts 50-64, Circa 1965 (Box 5, Folder 17)
        - Campaign operations, districts 65-69, Circa 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
        - Campaign operations, districts 70-79, Circa 1965 (Box 6, Folder 2)
        - Campaign operations, districts 80-89, Circa 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
        - Campaign operations, districts 90-95, Circa 1965 (Box 6, Folder 4)
        - Campaign operations, general, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5-7)
        - Canvass returns, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8-9)
        - Internal memos, 1965 July-September (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
        - Poll watching, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 3)
        - Sound equipment, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
        - Telephone canvass instructions, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 5)
        - Volunteers, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 6)
        - Voter registration, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      - Financial documents
        - Assembly district headquarters finances, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 8)
        - Check book, 1965 May-1968 December (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
        - Committee for Outstanding Governmental Candidates, 1965-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Contributions, undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Deficit, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 1)
        - Expense journal, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 2)
        - Finance committee, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 3)
        - Pay roll, undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
        - Personal account books, undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
        - Petty cash, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 6)
        - Reimbursed expenses, Circa 1965 (Box 9, Folder 7)
        - Storefront campaign office expenses, districts 20-46, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
        - Storefront campaign office expenses, districts 47-74, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 9)
        - Storefront campaign office expenses, districts 75-95, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 10)
        - Storefront campaign offices, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Constantine Sidamon-Eristoff papers
      - Notes
        - General, undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
        - Campaign, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 3)
        - Executive salaries, 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
        - Journals, 1964-1966, undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
        - Notebooks, 1967-1971 (Box 10, Folder 6-7)
        - Job file, Circa 1966-1967 (Box 10, Folder 8)
        - Senator Robert Dole, Circa 1984 (Box 10, Folder 9)
        - Transportation Administration, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 10)
        - Transportation Administration appointment, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 1)
        - Transportation Administration, personal, 1966-1968 (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Speeches
        - 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
        - 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4-5)
        - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
      - Reports
        - "Public Transportation - A Recommended Policy for the City of New York", 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
        - "Transportation Administration - 1971 and Thereafter" (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Correspondence
        - 1965 May-1970 October (Box 11, Folder 9)
        - 1970 November-1975 May (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Subject files
        - Adams, Peter D. research paper request, 1965 (Box 11, Folder 11)
        - Asphalt scandal/FBI, 1972-1975 (Box 11, Folder 12)
        - Balls and dinners, 1966-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1-3)
        - Bed-Stuy Rover Boys, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 4)
        - Booth, Betsy, Circa 1965-1971 (Box 12, Folder 5)
        - Borough presidents' attacks on superagencies, 1968-1973 (Box 12, Folder 6)
        - Byline, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - Campaign literature - New York City municipal elections, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 8)
        - Committee for Better New York City Government, 1965 May 26 (Box 12, Folder 9)
        - Conservative tactics, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 10)
        - Department of Highways, Circa 1966 (Box 12, Folder 11)
        - Election Watcher's Companion, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 12)
        - Gibney, Vincent J., 1970-1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
        - Gripe Line, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 14)
        - Lindsay, John Vliet legacy, 1968-2001 (Box 12, Folder 15)
        - Morningside Heights Republican Club, 1963-1965 (Box 13, Folder 1)
        - Parking Violations Bureau, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        - Political precedent, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
        - Poll watcher button case, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 4)
        - Puerto Rican-Hispanic Friends of Lindsay, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
        - San Francisco Trip, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 6)
        - Sidamon-Eristoff, Constantine - biography, Circa 1967 (Box 12, Folder 7)
        - South Bronx Republican Club, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 8)
        - Vito P. Battista v. James M. Power, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Additional material, 1966-1971; Accession 2016-M-075
  - Scrapbooks, 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1, Box 2)